* Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Mouse Sensitivity ("us", "we", or "our") operates the mouse-sensitivity.com website (the "Service").

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Information Collection And Use**  
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name ("Personal Information").

**Single Sign-On**  
Accounts can be linked to several third-party services that provides single sign-on capabilities. These services include, but are not limited to; Google, Microsoft, Twitter and Facebook. Linking your account to these services gives us access to information such as profile updates, profile pictures and email addresses. This information is never shared with any other party. When an account is linked, a token is acquired that allows for the single sign-on to take place. Your credentials to the third-party services are not stored.

**Log Data**  
We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service's functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.

**Cookies**  
This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.

**Security**  
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. As such we make no warranties as to the level of security afforded to your data, except that we will always act in accordance with the relevant legislation.

**Account deletion and PII Data request**

You can request PII Data and your account to be deleted [here](https://www.mouse-sensitivity.com/settings/account-security/). When your account is deleted, all related data such as posts, likes and status updates is deleted and not able to be recovered.

**Links To Other Sites**

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

**Third Parties**

**SparkPost**

SparkPost is used by this website to process and deliver emails.  

### Third Parties

**Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

**SendGrid**

SendGrid is used by this website to process and deliver emails.

**Antispam by Cleantalk**

This site uses the CleanTalk Anti-Spam service to protect the site from spam. The service uses Cookies and receives some information about the site visitor's browser and other data such as user name, e-mail addresses, IP and some other.

* Privacy Policy

    *  English (USA) (Default)
        
    *  English (UK)
        
    *  Deutsch von Inzomnia
        
    *  Español por Santiago Ramírez
        
    *  Français par Matsuho
        
    *  Italiano da Kytan
        
    *  Nederlands door Menthalion
        
    *  Norsk
        
    *  Polski
        
    *  Português (BR) por IBonato
        
    *  Русский от Merinda18
        
    *  Türkçe, Pyroxia tarafından
        
    *  简体中文，1kFace8aby提供
        
    *  繁體中文，1kFace8aby提供
        
    *  日本語
        
    *  한국어
        
    *  Main Theme (Default)
        
    *  Main Theme beta

Copyright © 2013-2024 Mouse Sensitivity [Powered by Invision Community](https://www.invisioncommunity.com/ "Invision Community")

x

* #### [Calculator](#)
    
* #### [Store](#)
    
* #### [Activity](#)

* Create New...

Privacy Manager
